{
    "subject": "resource/Sidney_Toler",
    "predicate": "property/spouse",
    "object": "Viva Tattersall",
    "human_readable": "Sidney Toler was married to Viva Tattersall.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884899258613586,
            "question": "Was Viva Tattersall married to Sidney Toler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9879006147384644,
            "question": "Was there a marriage between Sidney Toler and Viva Tattersall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9309377074241638,
            "question": "Who was married to Sidney Toler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9278797507286072,
            "question": "To whom was Sidney Toler married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921212375164032,
            "question": "Who was Sidney Toler married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8645891547203064,
            "question": "Sidney Toler's spouse was who?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.836934506893158,
            "question": "Who was Sidney Toler's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8255707621574402,
            "question": "Name Sidney Toler's wife."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6951870918273926,
            "question": "What is the name of Sidney Toler's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6951870918273926,
            "question": "What is the name of Sidney Toler's wife?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sidney Toler was married to Viva Tattersall.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1957_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Sidney Toler's wife?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1957_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name Sidney Toler's wife.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1957_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Sidney Toler's spouse?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1957_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1957_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Sidney Toler and Viva Tattersall had a relationship, with specific mentions of their marriage in the years 1943."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}